<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Smart Golf Manager</string>
    <string name="action_settings"></string>
    <string name="text_member_change">Member Change</string>
    <string name="text_party_registration">Party Registration</string>
    <string name="text_competition_registration">Competition Registration</string>
    <string name="text_bet_registration"> Bet Registration</string>
    <string name="text_course_name">Course Name</string>
    <string name="text_hole">Hole</string>
    <string name="not_entered">Not Entered</string>
    <string name="fellow_competitor_name">Fellow Competitor\'s Name</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="confirming">Confirming</string>
    <string name="create_competition">Create Competition</string>
    <string name="view_competition">View Competition</string>
    <string name="join_competition">Join Competition</string>
    <string name="create_group">Create Group</string>
    <string name="view_group">View Groups</string>
    <string name="course_registration">Course Registration</string>
    <string name="create_courses">Create Courses</string>
    <string name="view_courses">View Courses</string>
    <string name="course_name">Course Name</string>
    <string name="holes">Holes</string>
    <string name="par">Par</string>
    <string name="handicap">Handicap</string>
    <string name="course_created">Course Created</string>
    <string name="something_went_wrong">Something went Wrong</string>
    <string name="create_course_name">Create Course Name</string>
    <string name="up_to_18_holes">Up to 18 holes</string>
    <string name="Edit">Edit</string>
    <string name="loading_courses">Loading Courses</string>
    <string name="courses_loaded">Courses Loaded</string>
    <string name="loading_course_info">Loading Course Info</string>
    <string name="deleting_course">Deleting Course</string>
    <string name="course_deleted">Course Deleted</string>
    <string name="information_loaded">Information Loaded</string>
    <string name="enter_course_name">Enter Course Name</string>
    <string name="sure">Sure</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="help_content">Near Pin The one who get closest to the pin by one on in short hole get point/s from the fellow competitor/s. Second Near Pin The one who get closest to the pin by the second shot in middle hole get point/s from the follow competitor/s. Drive Competition The one who made a drive with a longest carry with tee shot get point/s from the fellow competitor/s. (usually apply for only ones who could be on fair way) Shortest Drive The one who made a drive with a shortest carry with tee shot gives point/s to other fellow competitor/s. Olympic This is a single-put match. Set prize Gold, Silver, Copper and Iron in order to the most far from cup and each player can have 4, 3, 2, 1 point. The tip-in shall be a diamond and can get 5 points form the fellow competitor/s. If there are a player/s who could archive all prizes (Gold to Iron) in the round shall be called GRAND SLAM and get 10 points from the fellow competitor/s. Scrap-Iron This usually play as an option of Olympic. If the player miss a putt of Iron, give a point to the fellow competitor/s. Under-Ground Olympic If a player made 3 putt in Olympic, the gold player gives 1 point, the silver gives 2 points, copper gives 3 points and iron gives 4 points to the fellow competitor/s. Skins-Match The top play in each hole can get 1 point from the competitor/s. If there are 2 top players, the point shall be carried over to next hole. Monte Carlo After the declaration, If the player could make up and down, the player can get 1 point from the fellow competitor/s. Two putt is 0 but if the player made 3 putt, he/she gives 1 point to the fellow competitor/s. Sandwich If the player could make up and down from bunker, the player can get 1 point form the fellow competitor/s. One Flag Upon the declaration to putt more than 1 putt, if the player could make one putt, the player can get 1 point from the fellow competitor/s. Horizontal Top player in each hole gets 1 point from the fellow competitor/s. Vertical Gives points equivalent to the difference in net score to the fellow competitor/s. Friend Compete with total score of each pair which decided by tee shot in each hole. If 2 players\' tee shots curve right side, these players become a pair. Curving to left side is also the same. So there is possibility to have different pair in each hole. Las Vegas Decide pairs with the same method to Friend. Make two digits number with the score in a pair. Put a lower score into tens place and higher score into ones place within a pair and point/s is equivalent to the difference between the pairs. Hussein(The Gulf War) The second player in each hole become Hussein and compete with other 3 (Allied). Give point/s equivalent to the difference; Hussein\'s score X 3 - total score of allied players. In with good fortune! Out with the demons When 3 players\' scores are the same and one player\'s score is worth, give 1 point to each fellow competitor. When 3 players\' scores are the same and one player\'s score is better, get 1 point from each fellow competitor. This rule is applicable on each hole and/or the total. A Cricket Give point/s to the fellow competitor/s when shot rough to rough. A Woodcutter, Woodpecker Gives point/s to the fellow competitor/s when hit the tree on your escaping shot from woods. A divorced wife Gives point/s when the ball go into neighboring course. The first bunker Gives point/s to the fellow competitor/s when ball go into bunker first time in the play. A Flounder Gives point/s to the fellow competitor/s when the player could not escape from bunker at 1 time. Ai○s OB and/or 3 putts are thought as a virus and carry over up to the 9th hole. Gives point/s to the fellow competitor/s equivalent to the number of the virus. A Snake Only 3 putts is thought as a virus and carrying over. Other rules are the same to Ai○s. A mole Only sand shot is thought as virus and carrying over. Other rules are the same to Ai○s. Honest John The players declare target score of the day before the starting. If archiving the target exactly, 0 point, if more than the target, the point/s equivalent to the difference, if less than the target, the point/s equivalent to 2 times of the difference, and the one who have least point (honest John) gets all the points from the fellow competitors. Red and White War Separate into some teams and compete with average score of the NET. Sink The player/s gives 5 points to organizer if the player/s\' tee shot could not be carried more than smoke ball in ceremonial opening shot. Chicken BBQ The one/s who could not be an owner through 9 holes give/s point/s to the fellow competitor/s. Imperial Army The one/s who used English within the game give/s point/s to the fellow competitor/s. Shooting Star In the case, only one player shot into rough with his/her tee shot (if it is a short hole, could not make the green in one shot), gives 1 point to the fellow competitor/s. The little princess In the case, only one player could shot onto fairway with his/her tee shot (if it is a short hole, could make the green in one shot), gets 1 point from the fellow competitor/s. Speeding Gives point/s to the fellow competitor/s when shot onto cart way and the ball jumped. OctopusSquidCentipede Gives point/s to the fellow competitor/s when shot the ground hardly.</string>
    <string name="type_bet">Type of Bet</string>
    <string name="prev">Prev</string>
</resources>